articleset.com 2017-10-02

# Privacy Policy | Call Loop

We keep your information safe and secure.

Your privacy is important, so Call Loop has created the following Privacy Policy to let you know what information we collect when you visit our website, why we collect it and how it is used.

The terms "you," "your," and "yours" refer to the customer using our website. The terms "Company," "we," "us," and "our" refer to Call Loop. This Privacy Policy is governed by our Terms of Service. By using this website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. We may periodically make changes to this Privacy Policy that we will include on this page. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy frequently and remain informed about any changes to it, so we encourage you to visit this page often.

### How do we use this information?

This information is used for internal marketing purposes only. Call Loop does not sell, exchange, or release your personal information (name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit data, etc.) Your information is not shared with any other third party or company outside of billing and shipping purposes.

### What are cookies and how does Call Loop use them?

Cookies help track a person's "session" while online. By showing how and when our visitors use this Site, this information can help us to continue to improve our Site. We will only use cookies to view information on your hard drive that was put there by a cookie from this Site. The use of cookies is an industry standard and many web sites use them. Cookies are stored on your computer and not on this Site. If you do not wish to receive cookies, or want to be notified of when they are placed, you may set your web browser to do so, if your browser permits.

### Is The Information Shared or Disclosed?

Call Loop is not in the business of selling your information. We consider this information to be a vital part of our relationship with you. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your personally identifiable information with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below: 

  * **Third Party Applications and Services:** If you elect to use one or more third party applications that interoperate with Call Loop's service via Call Loop Connect, those applications may upon your election be given access to data (which may include personally identifiable information) on Call Loop's systems generated in connection with your use of Call Loop's service. Please remember that Call Loop is not responsible for the policies and practices of third party application providers, and Call Loop shall have no liability arising from any action of any such provider as it concerns your data or information or otherwise. In connection with your use of any such third party applications, please review carefully the applicable privacy policies each such third party application provider to become familiar with their policies and practices as it concerns your data and information.

  * **Business Transfers:** As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, personally identifiable information may be part of the transferred assets. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer or successor of Call Loop may continue to use your information as set forth in this policy.
  * **Related Companies:** We may also share your personally identifiable information with any entity that is affiliated with us for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.
  * **Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties:** Call Loop, like many businesses, sometimes uses other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include mailing information, maintaining databases and processing payments. When we employ another company to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function.
  * **Legal Requirements and Other Circumstances:** Call Loop may disclose your personally identifiable information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of Call Loop, (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Call Loop website or services or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability.

### Is our contact database secure?

We will never sell, rent or market to your personal contact information for any marketing purposes whatsoever. Your information is 100% safe, secure, and all information is encrypted and transmitted without risk using a Secure Sockets Layer protocol.

Any information sent to Call Loop for text messaging and or storage purposes will remain the property of the account holder, which Call Loop will hold securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law. Call Loop will at no time collect or redistribute this information without your consent, except where legally required to do so by law.

### How does Call Loop protect our privacy?

Your information is stored at the list server that delivers Call Loop newsletters. Your information can only be accessed by those who help manage those lists in order to deliver e-mail to those who would like to receive Call Loop's newsletters.

All of the newsletters that are sent to you by Call Loop include an unsubscribe link in them. You can remove yourself at any time from our newsletters by clicking on the unsubscribe link. You can also contact us at support (at) CallLoop.com to change your information at any time.

This policy may be changed at any time at Call Loop's discretion. If we should update this policy, we will post the updates to this page on our Website.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy please direct them to support (at) CallLoop.com.

### Links to Other Sites

This website may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that Call Loop is not responsible for the privacy policies of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies only to information collected by this website.

### Your Consent To This Privacy Policy

By using Call Loop, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. Our Terms of Service take precedence over any conflicting Privacy Policy provision. We may change this Privacy Policy by posting a new version of this Privacy Policy on this website which it is your responsibility to review. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are protecting the personally identifiable information we collect. Your continued use of this website or Call Loop's services constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

### Legal Disclaimer

Call Loop operates "AS-IS" and "AS-AVAILABLE," without liability of any kind. Call Loop is not responsible for events beyond our direct control.

### Contacting Call Loop

If you believe that Call Loop has not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at support@CallLoop.com or by postal mail at Call Loop Inc., 310 SE 1st Street, Delray Beach, FL 33445 and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to remedy the problem.

### Last Updated

April 12th, 2014
